Rufus W. Weaver papers, Inclusive: 1906-1947, undated, Bulk: 1925-1945, undated
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
Rufus W. Weaver papers
Inclusive: 1906-1947, undated, Bulk: 1925-1945, undated
Baylor University, The Texas Collection http://www.baylor.edu/lib/texas/
3178
Weaver, Rufus W., 1870 - 1947
6 document boxes.
This collection contains materials produced by Dr. Rufus W. Weaver, a noted Southern Baptist pastor, educator, and cultural commentator. Weaver was the president of Mercer University, and his later church-state work led directly to the founding of the Baptist Joint Committee on Public Affairs.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Average.
Biography/Profile
Rufus Washington Weaver was born in Greensboro, North Carolina, on 1870 June 3. As a young man, Weaver worked as a printer and a journalist. Weaver received an A.B. and M.A. from Wake Forest College in 1893, a Th.D. from Southern Baptist Seminary in 1899, and four additional degrees between 1912 and 1920. He married Charlotte Mason Payne in 1911.
All the while, Weaver was both pastoring Baptist churchesDLfrom North Carolina to Ohio to MarylandDLand beginning a longstanding involvement in Baptist education. Weaver started by teaching high school, moved on to leadership of the Baptist Education Board in Tennessee, and eventually became the president of Georgia’s Mercer University, a position he held from 1918 to 1927. During and after his time at Mercer, Weaver remained active in the educational work of the Southern Baptist Convention, and in his later years he instructed graduate students at the American University in Washington, DC.
After he left Mercer University, most of Weaver’s professional work took place in the nation’s capital and centered on the relationship of church and state. A prolific author, Weaver published numerous books and pamphlets on the relationship of Christianity to American culture, including a collection of sermons titled The Christian Faith at the Nation’s Capital (1936). Weaver also had key leadership roles in the District of Columbia Baptist Convention and the Southern Baptist Committee on Public Relations. The latter organizationDLtogether with similar committees from the Northern Baptist Convention and the National Baptist Convention USA, Inc.DLwas later subsumed into the Baptist Joint Committee on Public Affairs, which in turn maintained and then donated Weaver's personal papers to Baylor University. Rufus W. Weaver died in Washington, DC, on 1947 January 31.
Scope and Content
This collection consists of written and printed materials produced by Rufus W. Weaver between 1906 and 1947. Most of these materials are formal documentsDLtexts prepared for publication or oral deliveryDLand most relate to Weaver’s ongoing engagement with Southern Baptist education and public policy. The first and third series are roughly equal in size, and together take up the vast majority of the collection. The materials are in average condition.
The first series, Series I. “An Introduction to Christianity” Manuscript, contains tables of contents and chapter drafts for an unpublished manuscript which Weaver seems to have begun in the late 1920s and continued writing into the 1940s. Though the exact scope and purpose of this work remain uncertain, the manuscript seems to provide a systematic overview of world history, world religions, and the history and philosophy of Christianity more specifically. There are multiple iterations of most chapter drafts, often with multiple titles or numbering systems, and these variants are indicated in the folder titles.
The second series, Series II. Mercer University, contains the texts of addresses, statements, and articles written by Weaver during his time as the president of Mercer University (1918-1927). A large number of these documents are historical sketches meant to communicate the importance of Mercer University to Georgia Baptists and to Southern Baptists more broadly.
The final series, Series III. Christianity and Culture, contains the remainder of Weaver’s literary productions, including addresses, lectures, notes, pamphlets, and sermons. The contents of this series are more varied than those of the previous two, but nearly all revolve around the relationship of the Baptist faith to American culture. Many of the documents in this series lack titles and dates, and several are incomplete.
Arrangement
Prior to current processing, this collection was arranged in titled folders which were grouped into five series: “An Introduction to Christianity” Manuscript, Mercer University Items, Church-State Materials, Baptists Papers, and Miscellaneous Items. An initial inventory, found within the collection, suggests that the materials arrived in no particular order and were then arranged into these five groups through an earlier round of processing.
To preserve any remaining original order, the latest processing has made minimal modifications to the collection’s preexisting organization. At a basic level, the materials have been refoldered and retitled for more specificity. Additionally, the first two seriesDLSeries I. “An Introduction to Christianity” Manuscript and Series II. Mercer UniversityDLhave been adopted, while the third through fifth series have been combined into one series, Christianity and Culture.
Access Restrictions
All requests for copying of materials must be submitted to The Texas Collection in writing. Please use the Request Form for Copying Materials sheet. Unpublished materials authored or otherwise produced by the creator (s) of this collection are in the public domain. There are no restrictions on use. Copyright status for other collection materials is unknown. Transmission or reproduction of materials protected by U.S. Copyright Law (Title 17, U.S.C.) beyond that allowed by fair use requires the written permission of the copyright owners. Works not in the public domain cannot be commercially exploited without permission of the copyright owners. Responsibility for any use rests exclusively with the user.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. 3178. Acquired 1995-05-12
Related Resources
Related collection materials
Weaver’s personal papers should be consulted in conjunction with two other sources: his executive director series within the Baptist Joint Committee records (Accession #3193, The Texas Collection, Baylor University) and his papers located at the Southern Baptist Historical Library and Archives (#AR 99).
Related references
Find A Grave, Inc. “Rufus Washington Weaver.” Memorial #60275196. Databases. Accessed 2017 August 11.
“Rufus W. Weaver.” Western Recorder, 1943 April 22.
“Rufus Washington Weaver.” Rufus W. Weaver papers, Accession #3193, Box #5, Folder #45, The Texas Collection, Baylor University.
Smith, John Chabot. “An Ideal is Dr. Rufus Weaver’s Taskmaster.” The Washington Post, 1939 December 31.
Index Terms
Subjects (Persons)
Weaver, Rufus Washington, 1870-1947.
Subjects (Organizations)
Baptist Joint Committee on Public Affairs.
Subjects
Baptists -- Clergy -- Archives.; Baptists -- Education (Higher) -- United States; Baptists -- Sermons.; Baptists -- United States -- History -- 20th century.; Church and state.
Genres
Articles.; Manuscripts.; Notes (documents); Pamphlets.; Speeches.
- "An Introduction to Christianity" Manuscript, circa 1946, undated; 1
  Administrative Information
  Physical Description
  General condition: Average.
  Biography/Profile
  This series contains a book manuscriptDLincluding tables of contents, chapter drafts, and bibliographiesDLwritten by Rufus W. Weaver between the 1920s and the 1940s. The book appears to be an overarching summary of religion’s historic role in culture, with a particular focus upon Christianity. This series is in average condition.
  - Manuscript Outline: “An Introduction to Christianity”, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Tables of Contents: “An Introduction to Christianity,” “Religion and the Religions,” and “The Genesis of Christianity”, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Tables of Contents: “The Genesis of Christianity” and “Christianity, Its Genesis and Its Expansion”, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Tables of Contents: “The Religions”, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Tables of Contents: “Christian History and the Spirit of the Age” and “The Human Influences Affecting the Historical Development of Christianity”, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Tables of Contents: “Present Day Christianity”, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Tables of Contents: “The History of Christian Thought”, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Prospective Manuscript Outlines: “An Introduction to Christianity” and “New Subjects That May Be Considered”, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Introduction: “Religion and the Religions”, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Introduction/Chapter 1 Drafts: “The Modern Approach to the Study of Religion” and “Religion and the Modern Mind”, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Introduction and Chapter 2 Drafts: “An Introduction to Christianity” and “What is Religion?”, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Chapter 1/2 Drafts: “Representative Modern Attitudes Towards Religion”, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Chapter 2/3 Drafts: “Science and Religion,” “The Sciences of Religion,” and “The Scientific Study of Religion”, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Chapter 2/3/4 Drafts: “Current Definitions of Religion,” “The Definition of Religion,” “Some Definitions of Religion,” and “Modern Definitions of Science and Religion”, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Chapter 4/5 Drafts: “The Region of Religion”, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Chapter 5/6 Drafts: “The Function of Religion” and “The Region of Religion”, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Chapter 4/5/7 Drafts: “The Nature of Religion”, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Chapter 8/11/12/13 Drafts: “The Philosophy of Religion”, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Chapter 9/12/90 Drafts: “The Basic Problems of Religion” and “The Problems of Religion”, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Chapter 7/8/10 Drafts: “The Classification of the Religions” and “The Classifications of the Religions”, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Chapter 10/11 Drafts: “The Gradations of the Religions”, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Chapter 12 Drafts: “The Tests of the Religions”, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Chapter 13/14 Drafts: “The Religions of the World”, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Chapter 13 Drafts: “The Races of Men”, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Chapter 5/6/14/15 Drafts: “The Mind of the Uncivilized Man” and “The Mind of the Civilized Man”, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Chapter 6 Drafts: “Primitive Monotheism”, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Chapter 7 Drafts: “The Idea of God as Held by Most Primitive Peoples” and “The Idea of God as Held by the Most Primitive Peoples”, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Chapter 15 Drafts: “The Interpretations of Tribal Religions”, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Chapter 16/17/18 Drafts: “Conflicting Elements in Tribal Religions,” “Conflicting Interpretations of Tribal Religions,” and “The Neglect of ‘The High Gods of the Low Races’”, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Chapter 16 Draft: “The Nature, Attributes and Worship of the Primitive High God”, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Chapter 17 Draft: “The Religions of the Nations”, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Chapter 18/19/20 Drafts: “The Religion of Egypt”, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Chapter 19/20/21 Drafts: “The Religion of Babylonia and Assyria”, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Chapter 20/21/22 Drafts: “The Religions of Greece and Rome”, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Chapter 21/22/23 Drafts: “The Religions of Ancient Iran and India”, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Chapter 23/24 Drafts: “The Religion of Ancient China and Japan”, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Chapter 23/24/25 Drafts: “The Religion of the Seers or the Law Givers”, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Chapter 24/25/26 Drafts: “Confucianism, The Ethical System of Confucius and Taoism, The Religion of Lao-Tse”, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Chapter 25/26/27 Drafts: “Zoroastrianism, The Religion of Zarathustra”, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Chapter 26/27/28 Drafts: “Buddhism, The Religion of Gautama”, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Chapter 27/28 Drafts: “Islam, The Religion of Mohammed”, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Chapter 28/29 Drafts: “The Religion of Israel or The Religion of Moses and the Prophets,” “Judaism, The Religion of Moses and the Prophets,” and “Judaism, The Religion of Moses, the Prophets and the Rabbis”, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Chapter 29/30 Drafts: “Judaism, The Religion of the Jewish Rabbis” and “Later Judaism, The Religion of the Jewish Rabbis”, undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Chapter 21/30/31 Drafts: “Christianity and the Other Religions”, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Chapter 31/32 and Appendix A Drafts: “The Source Material for a Life of Jesus”, undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Chapter 32/33 Draft: “The World In Which Jesus Lived”, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Chapter 33/34 Drafts: “The Life of Jesus” and “From the Birth to the Baptism of Jesus”, undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Chapter 43/44 Drafts: “The Validation of the Evangelical Experience”, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Chapter 45 Draft: “The Christian Life in the Apostolic Period”, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Chapter 62 Draft: “The Preaching of the Gospel”, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Chapter 69 Draft: “The Greek Formulation of the Christian Faith”, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Chapter 70 Draft: “The Latin Formulation of the Christian Faith”, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Chapter 71 Draft: “The Protestant or Teutonic Formulation of the Christian Faith”, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Chapter 72 Draft: “The Ascetic Pursuit of Christian Piety”, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Chapter 73 Draft: “The Secularized Pursuit of Christian Piety”, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Chapter 74 Draft: “The Emancipated Pursuit of Mystical Christian Piety”, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Chapter 75 Draft: “The Piety That Produced Modern Missions”, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Table of Contents and Chapter 46/61 Drafts: “The Human Influences Affecting the Historical Development of Christianity” and “The Mind of Christ”, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Chapter 62 Draft: “The Apostolic Mind”, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Chapter 63 Draft: “The Judaizing Mind”, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Chapter 64 Draft: “The Gentile Mind”, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Chapter 65 Draft: “The Hellenistic Mind”, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Chapter 66 Draft: “The Theological Mind”, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Chapter 67 Draft: “The Roman Mind”, undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Chapter 68 Draft: “The Sacerdotal Mind”, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Chapter 69 Draft: “The Ecclesiastical Mind”, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Chapter 70 Draft: “The Protestant Mind”, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Chapter 71 Draft: “The Nationalistic Mind”, undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Chapter 72 Draft: “The Emancipating Mind”, undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Chapter 74 Drafts: “The Denominational Mind”, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Chapter 60/75 Drafts: “The Scientific Mind”, undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Chapter 3 Draft: “The Situation Modern Christianity Confronts", circa 1946 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Chapter 78 Draft: “The Modern Denominational Expression of the Christian Life”, undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Chapter 79 Draft: “The History of Christian Apologetics”, undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Chapter 80 Draft: “The Evangelical Christian Experience”, undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Chapter 81 Draft: “The Postulations That Condition Human Experience”, undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Chapter 81/82 Drafts: “The Validation of Human Beliefs”, undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Chapter 83/84 Drafts: “The Validation of Human Values”, undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Chapter 83 Drafts: “Creative Idealization”, undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Chapter 84/85 Drafts: “The Theoretical Bases of Morality”, undated (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Chapter 85/86 Drafts: “The Christian Approach to Ultimate Reality”, undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Chapter 86 Draft: “The Problem of Evil”, undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Chapter 87 Drafts: “The Scientific Bases of Christian Faith”, undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Chapter 88 Draft: “The Essence of Christianity”, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Chapter 90 Draft: “The Finality of the Christian Religion”, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Chapter 15 Draft: “Religion and Philosophy”, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Chapter 13/14/16/89 Drafts: “The Christian Revelation of God”, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Chapter 16 Draft: “A Christian Interpretation of God for the Twentieth Century Mind”, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Chapter 8 Drafts: “The Scientific and Rationalistic Interpretations of Religion” and “Scientific and Rationalistic Interpretations of Religion”, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Chapter 9 Drafts: “The Dynamic Interpretation of Religion”, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Chapter 2 Draft: “The Relation of the Christian Religion to its Social Environment”, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Chapter 72 Draft: “The Relation of Christianity to the Social Order”, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Chapter 61 Draft: “The Historic Backgrounds of the Present Issue in Religion”, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Chapter 67 Draft: “The Bible of Early Christianity”, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Chapter 68 Draft: “The Influence of the Bible”, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Chapter 3/4/16/17 Drafts: “Scientific Theories of the Genesis of Religion” and “The Interpretations of Tribal Religions”, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Chapter 7-15 Appendices: “Subjects for Further Study”, circa 1930s (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Mercer University, 1921-1929, undated; 2
  This series includes addresses, articles, statements, and other documents produced by Rufus Weaver while he was the president of Georgia’s Mercer University (1918-1927). Many of these documents relate to Mercer’s role in establishing Baptist churches, colleges, and seminaries across the South. The series is in average condition.
  - Biographical Address on Jesse Mercer, 1927 August (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - “Jesse Mercer, The Leader Who Laid Lasting Foundations”, undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - “Joshua Mercer: The Pioneer Baptist Leader of Florida”, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - “Adiel Sherwood, The Spiritual Founder of Mercer University”, undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - “Adiel Sherwood: A Sainted Yankee who Invaded the South”, undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Fiftieth Anniversary Materials: Dr. Albert Henry Newman, 1926-1927 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Address to the Georgia Press Association, circa 1926 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Mercer University Press Release, 1927 September 17 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Mercer University Business Office Bulletin, 1927 July 6 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Mercer University Bulletin: “The Issue Which Has Emerged”, 1925 September 1 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Mercer University Commencement Notice, undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Mercer University Commencement Address: “The Moulders of Public Opinion”, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Notes on the Role of Baptists and Mercer University in American Higher Education, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - “The Place of Macon in the Building of a Greater Wesleyan [College]”, undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Augusta Chronicle: Article: “Mercer University Extends the Helping Hand”, 1927 April (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Rotary Club Address on Public Education in Georgia, circa 1924 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Palaver Club Address: “Religious Beginnings in Georgia”, undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - “The Future of Denominational Education Today Hangs in the Balance”, undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Outline: “The Vision of Christian Education”, undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - “Contributions Which Mercer Has Made”, undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Mercer University Baccalaureate Address: “The Meaning of Mercerianism”, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - “The Mercerian Age”, undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Mercer University Commencement Address: “The Mercerian Interpretation of Life”, undated (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Address to the Georgia Baptist Convention: “The Place of Mercer University in Solving the Problem which Georgia Baptists Now Face”, circa 1926 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - “Mercer University in 1850”, undated (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Letter on the Accreditation of Mercer University, 1927 May 19 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - “Growth of Mercer University Accompanied by Growth of Baptists”, undated (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - “The Theological Seminary of Mercer University”, undated (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence on the Accreditation of Mercer University, 1921 February-March (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - “Baptist Life in Georgia Ninety Years Ago”, circa 1929 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Pamphlet: “The Religious Affiliation of Students Enrolled for the Fall Term, 1927 in The Senior Colleges and Universities of the South”, circa 1928 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Incomplete Address Drafts on Religious Education, undated (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Mercer University Convocation Address, 1927 September (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Paper on Educational Standards of Southern Baptists and the Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools Within the Southern States, circa 1920s (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Address: “A Permanent Educational Program for Georgia”, circa 1920s (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Outline: “The Permanent Educational Program of Georgia Baptists”, circa 1920s (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Christianity and Culture, 1906-1947, undated; 3
  This series is comprised of the lecture and research notes, addresses, statements, and sermons of Rufus W. Weaver. Most of these materials were produced during Weaver’s later years, while he was living in Washington, but some relate to his early pastoral ministry. This series is in average condition.
  - Table of Contents: Church-State Sermons, undated (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - “The Administrative Policy of the District of Columbia Baptist Convention”, circa 1943 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Magazine: The American Protestant: Dedicated to the Cause of Religious Liberty with Complete Separation of Church and State, 1940 July (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Pamphlets: “The Baptist S.O.S. from Washington” and “The Story of Washington Baptists”, circa 1941 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Pamphlets: “Baptist Watchmen and the New World Order”, circa 1940s (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - New York Times: Newspaper Clipping: “Baptists Protest Link to Vatican”, 1939 December 29 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Address at the Southern Baptist Theological Seminary: “The Baptists and the New World Order”, circa 1944 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Palaver Club Address: “The Blitzkrieg Against God”, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Book Reviews: The Revolt Against God, 1944, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Sermon: “The Chiseling of the Church”, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Sermon: “Christian Stewardship of Private Property”, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Sermon: “Christianity and Capitalism”, circa 1935 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Sermon: “Christ’s Cure for Unemployment”, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Sermon: “Church and State” and “The True Relation of the Church to the State”, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Notes on Civilization and Religion, 1929, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - “An Evangelical Approach to Contemporary World Problems”, circa 1946 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Sermon: “Evangelical Religion, The Only Sure Ground of a Lasting Democracy”, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - The Religious Herald: University of Richmond Baccalaureate Address: “The Genius of Christianized Culture”, 1929 June 27 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - “How International Religious Liberty Was Lost in 1919”, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Poem: “The Humble Petition of a Country Poet”, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - List of Individuals Associated with International Brotherhood, undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - “The Most Urgent Problem in American Life”, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)